Wow, she's going to town on that bone.
I don't know where she gets them,
but she's been bringing them here to chew on.
Laika! What on earth are you doing?!
It's very dusty under there!
Please come out!
Fry Friends
The Hindsight Bones and the Snowy Dragon
We ended up fishing a
whole person's worth of bones
out from underneath my bed...
N-now hold on!
Laika doesn't eat people!
She FOUND those!
Are you lying...?
Laika tells the truth!
She might've nibbled on the bones...
Guilty, eh? Turn yourself in!
This wasn't Laika's doing!
The evidence says otherwise. Give it up!
L-leave me alone, pudge muffin!
Hey! I'll have you know that-
Boy, am I glad to be able to move again!
It's a-
A skeleton!
S-skeleton...?
...skeleton...
They're monsters made of bones!
When someone has unfinished business
or dies holding a deep-seated grudge,
they're resurrected as an undead creature!
In other words, this person is
also from another world?
That's exactly right!
My name is Honeda.
It's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Now then, little miss doggie...
I-I'm not a dog...
I appreciate you putting my body
back together for me!
The gnawing was unnecessary,
but collecting all of my bones
must have been back-breaking work,
so I forgive you!
Aw, who's a good girl?
She seems kind of nice,
don'tcha think?
Aw, who's a good girl?
Lighthearted... y'know,
being bones and all.
You are! Yes, you are!
Lighthearted... y'know,
being bones and all.
You are! Yes, you are!
She doesn't exactly strike me as
someone who has a grudge...
Oh, but I do!
You see, I was once a mage
in the service of a certain kingdom...
but one day, I was falsely
accused of treason
and hanged for my supposed crimes.
I returned as a skeleton,
and there was a doorway inside a dungeon
I'd stumbled upon that led to this world...
But the moment I arrived here...
I got hit by a truck and shattered to pieces.
Woe is me!
Don't cry, bony!
But now that I can move again,
I intend to enjoy this place!
Really? Looking like that?
O-oh, sorry...
No, you're right...
Anyone with eyes can see
that I've gotten fat!
You're a SKELETON!
Is it not obvious? Well, if I must...
Sh-she's... using magic to
give herself a body?!
Right on the money!
And by the way, this body is a recreation
of what I looked like when I was still alive.
See? My lower back is flabby...
I don't know what to do!
I'm far too embarrassed
to go out in public like this!
And all I wanted was to enjoy this place...
In that case, why not ask
Mr. Human for help?
This is his area of expertise.
I'd appreciate any assistance
you can provide!
Hm, it looks like your spine curves forward...
Sometimes bad posture is
the culprit behind stiff shoulders.
Slouching puts pressure on
your internal organs,
which can have negative consequences.
Do skeletons even have organs?
Cross my heart!
First, I'll teach you some effective
stretches for your lower back.
If you don't take the necessary precautions,
strength training can make things worse.
The first step is to loosen up your muscles
while being mindful of your posture.
Just like that! Try and do these
exercises at least once a day.
This stuff is pretty difficult...
I'll do it with you!
We'll give it our best shot!
Laika, too!
You guys...
This is exciting!
I'm more motivated than ever!
What do you think?
My back looks nice and slim!
You did a great job getting in shape!
You'll be able to enjoy
the human world now, right?
Enjoy it?
Well, that's what I'd hoped...
Huh?
The magic disguising her skeleton...!
In retrospect, when I turned into a skeleton...
I was alone for a long time.
Being alone makes you
reflect on a lot of things.
Pain, fear, sorrow, hatred...
The grief and the despair of
wondering why I alone
was forced to suffer such a fate...
But those dark and dismal feelings...
They disappeared as I
spent time with all of you.
Which is why I think...
...exercising helped me enjoy my time here.
I can finally rest now!
Thank you.
Bony went bye-bye...
So she was a fairy...
We ought to give her a decent burial.
Weight loss is a journey.
What lies beyond that is the important part.
Human...
I wanted Honeda to enjoy life...
I wanted more for her...
Do you really think so?
Well then count me in!
She spoke?!
Hooray!
Your words stirred up more feelings
of regret, so I came back again!
Thank goodness!
Your words stirred up more feelings
of regret, so I came back again!
Oh jeez...
Your words stirred up more feelings
of regret, so I came back again!
Without that fleshy baggage,
these old bones nearly gave up the ghost!
...I want a refund.
Plus-Sized Elf
Plus-Sized Elf!
Someone's in a good mood 'cause of the snow.
Why are we walking in this kind of weather...?
Are you okay?
I think something fell out of your-
Oh, I use dried lizards for my sorcery.
Sure, but why was it in your pocket?
Sneak, sneak, sneak...
There's a saying in the human world:
Hope for the best, prepare for the worst.
What's wrong?
Huh?
Ah, it's not like lizards
freak me out or anything-
Lizard.
Fine, I lied! I hate them!
I've hated reptiles ever since
a snake bit me when I was a kid!
I can't even look at them,
much less touch one!
Guess the human isn't invincible after all.
A little cliché, don't you think?
Oh, look at the time! I'd better get to work!
See ya! Don't wait up!
He ran away...
Well, we might as well finish our walk.
No, I'm going home! It's freezing...
You moron.
This is the perfect kind of day for-
Oof!
Owie...
What's this?
There's a person under there!
We have to help them!
We got her out of those
wet clothes, but, uh...
A dragon?!
So she's just sleeping?!
What was she doing
underneath all that snow...?
Oh, she's awake.
You two are elves...
What is this place?
Did she just... talk inside my head?!
Dragons are capable of wielding
higher forms of sorcery.
To someone like her,
telepathy is small potatoes.
Wanna eat beef... Wanna lose weight...
Hungry, want food...
Seems like we're catching
her excess thoughts...
Anyway, how did you end up
buried in the snow?
I believe it was after lunchtime.
I was on a walk...
but then I fell prey to drowsiness.
Why bother when it's snowing outside?
To lose weight, duh!
To lose weight.
Still, I never knew dragons
could be so rotund!
Come again, little girl?
Ow!
Stop that! You're going to piss her off!
So what?!
Haven't you ever heard of
a dragon's treasure?
Y'mean all the stuff they hoard
and stand guard over?
I'm starving... Wanna eat meat...
Y'mean all the stuff they hoard
and stand guard over?
If we get the human to help
the dragon lose weight...
there might be cash in our future.
I could reduce my hours at the corner store!
Treasure doesn't really interest me, so...
All-you-can-eat French fries.
I'LL DO IT!
You wish to lose weight, dragon?
Where'd that come from?
But yes, I suppose so...
There's only one man who can make it happen.
What? And who would that be?
He's known as...
The Dragon Slenderer!
My name is Gonda.
Nice to meet you. I'm Naoe.
Why did we have to hide her tail?
We don't have a choice!
She looks way too much like a reptile.
We absolutely cannot let him find out.
Strange. I hadn't expected the
Dragon Slenderer to be so young...
Huh? Dra-
Let's not waste valuable time!
Go ahead and hear her out!
Yeah! It's not like she's a dragon or anyth-
Keep your big mouth shut, wouldja?!
Well then, I'll start by examining you.
Whoa, you're freezing!
Your skin feels like a block of ice!
I can't lose weight if I'm cold?
It's not that.
You could develop hypothermia.
We need to warm you up first!
Calm down, human.
Lizards are cold-blooded animals.
Even if they-
Good idea! I'll go make her a hot drink.
The cold breeds all sorts of illnesses.
Make sure your body stays warm in order
to avoid a weakened immune system
as well as tension and swelling
caused by poor blood circulation.
I understand.
Cheers.
She has a forked-
I-it's extremely rude to stare, y'know!
Much warmer.
That's good!
Now, on to the main issue.
Are there any specific areas of your body
that you'd like to focus on?
I want to lose weight
around my belly and my hips.
My belly gets in the way
when I walk on all fours.
All fours...?
Th-this one's got a four-digit weight!
That's rich coming from
the lard-ass elf herself!
Zip it, butterball! Can you not
cause problems for like five seconds?!
Ladies, enough with the bickering!
I'm going to teach you some exercises
that tighten the waistline,
so let's do them together!
He doesn't suspect a thing.
You can tone your waist by engaging
the muscles around your stomach and hips.
But this type of activity
is taxing on the body,
so some people have
a tough time sticking with it.
That's the reason why
I recommend arm swinging!
Hip rolling exercises are a great option, too.
This is fairly difficult...
Don't forget to do the same amount
in the opposite direction.
Human! Y-yeah, uh, about that...!
Human...?
We lost him...
The human suffered, but we were successful.
Dragon.
What?
Remain consistent with these exercises
and you're guaranteed to lose weight.
Such is the wisdom of the Dragon Slenderer.
That deserves recognition, no?
So that's how it is...
Alright, fine. I concede.
Riches I collected here in the human world.
Dragon Gems
Keep them safe.
That's her precious treasure...?
Pretty marbles used to decorate
the top of a toilet sink basin
Farewell, Dragon Slenderer.
How much are these worth?
...they're priceless.